

CONTACT ME AT

- Autonomous City of Buenos Aires, Argentina
- brunomleguizamon@gmail.com
- www.brunomleguizamon.com.ar
- in /bruno-leguizamon
- /brunomleguizamon

LANGUAGES

- Basic English
- Native Spanish

SKILLS



JavaScript ES6

HTML 5

B Bootstrap

🤔 Python

OTHER SKILLS



mySQL

di Django

LEGUIZAMON BRUNO

WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hello World, I graduated from technical school. In my first work experiences I was trained in programming of telephone and fire exchanges as well as BMS. As I progressed in my career, I realized that my true passion was programming, which is why I did several online courses in a self-taught way and I did a Master in Python at the University of San Martin.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Development

Freelancer | nov 2020 - present

• Creating Web pages and Web apps

Mantenance Analyst

Anchorena's Sanatorium of San Martin | nov 2018 - present

- Programming, corrective and preventive maintenance in building management system (XML) facilities.
- Programming, corrective and preventive maintenance in access control facilities (XML)

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Web Development

Udemy | 2020

- JavaScript
- CSS3
- HTML5
- mySQL
- React

Programmer Technician

Universidad nacional de San Martin | 2020 - present

Electro-Mechanical Technician

E.E.S.T. N°4 - Emilio Mitre | 2010 - 2016